<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on NAIIVE</title>
    <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on NAIIVE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AISE</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/1_aise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/1_aise/</guid>
      <description>General linkAISE is a software built using the Godot Engine, offering users a suite of tools for image creation and modification. designed as a mobile application, its inception aimed to integrate cutting-edge artificial intelligence technology.
Resources AI features Online features Offline features url type description Itch.io page, HTML5 executable &amp;amp; more user friendly explanation Android installer as apk target platform IOS N/A target platform Windows portable as exe in zip for testing, main development operating system MacOS unknown as zip for testing, untested / reported Linux portable as x86_64 in zip for testing, untested / reported Use Stable Diffusion Served by AI Horde Models Text to Image Image to Image ControlNet Tiling &amp;amp; More LoRA by Civit AI Style Prompt injection using CheatSheet Discovery (Social) Reporting Tool Version Checking Text Translation Google Translate API Image Optimization Resmush API image editing sketch gallery Motivation linkAISE was initially constructed within a limited timeframe, with a maximum duration of one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motive</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/2_motive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/2_motive/</guid>
      <description> warning Caution - This page is in progress. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
