<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NAIIVE</title>
    <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NAIIVE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language><atom:link href="https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>At Glance</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_at_glance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 10:15:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_at_glance/</guid>
      <description>Pages linkExplore a wide range of content provided with a clean, readable, and enjoyable experience, all while minimizing cognitive load. we&amp;rsquo;re make sure that we&amp;rsquo;ve poured our hearts ❤️ into creating an environment that caters to your needs.
workspaces Service
develop, adapt, and manage technology you envision
deployed_code Projects
Technical explanation &amp; executable
stream Resources
Open resource, for public / general use
Design linkTo acquaint our visitors with documents and technical descriptions commonly encountered during technology adaptation, our website has been intentionally designed to resemble a documentation or admin panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f90_about_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f90_about_us/</guid>
      <description>NAIIVE is a decentralized organization operating across various fields.
Initially, NAIIVE was established in response to the opportunities where numerous talented individuals were underappreciated, lacked connections, or had limited choices, hindering their ability to nurture and capitalize on their talents.
One of the challenges for clients lies in the obscurity, difficulty in locating, lack of guarantees, or doubts associated with these talents, leading to missed opportunities and deals.
NAIIVE serves as an intermediary and a guarantor, facilitating collaboration between clients and these talents, ensuring that they can fully leverage their skills, while clients receive assurances regarding the sustainability of their projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>job</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f92_job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f92_job/</guid>
      <description>send a email to naiive@email.com We’re excited to hear from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f93_partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f93_partnership/</guid>
      <description>email : naiive@email.com / still.lkmn@hotmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
