<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NAIIVE</title>
    <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NAIIVE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:12:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naiiveprojects.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>At Glance</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_at_glance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 10:15:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_at_glance/</guid>
      <description>Pages linkExplore a wide range of content provided with a clean, readable, and enjoyable experience, all while minimizing cognitive load. we&amp;rsquo;re make sure that we&amp;rsquo;ve poured our hearts ❤️ into creating an environment that caters to your needs.
workspaces Service
develop, adapt, and manage technology you envision
deployed_code Projects
Technical explanation &amp; executable
stream Resources
Open resource, for public / general use
Design linkTo acquaint our visitors with documents and technical descriptions commonly encountered during technology adaptation, our website has been intentionally designed to resemble a documentation or admin panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/1_general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/1_general/</guid>
      <description>Overview linkTechnology is no longer an expensive or inaccessible resource. Unfortunately, this accessibility primarily benefits individuals or companies already established in the field.
Problem linkFor the majority of individuals or businesses, technology remains unfamiliar and out of reach. Yet, it&amp;rsquo;s undeniable that technology and automation play a crucial role in accelerating growth, enhancing efficiency, and ensuring survival.
Solution linkWe aim to bridge this gap by offering technology-related services powered by cutting-edge solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/2_request/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/2_request/</guid>
      <description>email : naiive@email.com / still.lkmn@hotmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ ID ] Virtual Tour</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/11_software/1_virtual_tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:12:15 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/11_software/1_virtual_tour/</guid>
      <description>warning this service only available in Indonesia, you can apply / request this service to be available in your country. Aplikasi Virtual Tour identik dengan luxury / membingungkan dimana hanya sebagian perusahaan / individu yang dapat memanfaatkannya, kami menawarkan jasa pengembangan / pembuatan virtual tour baik dalam bentuk jasa maupun pembuatan software untuk berbagai platform, yang dapat bersaing baik dari segi harga, kualitas, support, juga fleksibilitas.
di rekomendasikan untuk melihat layanan-layanan yang telah tersedia, berikut beberapa layanan dengan poin perbedaan dengan jasa yang kami tawarkan tanpa pengulangan poin yang di sampaikan :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AISE</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/1_aise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/1_aise/</guid>
      <description>General linkAISE is a software built using the Godot Engine, offering users a suite of tools for image creation and modification. designed as a mobile application, its inception aimed to integrate cutting-edge artificial intelligence technology.
Motivation linkAISE was initially constructed within a limited timeframe, with a maximum duration of one day. The primary objective was to swiftly incorporate state-of-the-art Artificial Intelligence technology for proof of concept and as a fundamental exercise in mobile device design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motive</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/2_motive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:08:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/2_motive/</guid>
      <description> warning Caution - This page is in progress. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAIIVE Website</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/1_naiive_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/1_naiive_website/</guid>
      <description>Thread link weight : int # thread weight for indexing title : string icon : string icon path. ref https://fonts.google.com/icons description : string lead : string date : date lastmod : date draft : bool images : array toc : bool Add Alerts linkPage alerts can be added to your markdown using the following shortcode:
{{&amp;lt; alert text=&amp;#34;This is the default alert. It consists of a default theme colour and icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nv.gd.core</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/2_nv.gd.core/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/2_nv.gd.core/</guid>
      <description>Brief linkNAIIVE.GODOT.Core is set of class, modules, &amp;amp; reusable objects we often use as starting point or to speed up development process
warning Caution - This page is in progress. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f90_about_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f90_about_us/</guid>
      <description>NAIIVE is a decentralized organization operating across various fields.
Initially, NAIIVE was established in response to the opportunities where numerous talented individuals were underappreciated, lacked connections, or had limited choices, hindering their ability to nurture and capitalize on their talents.
One of the challenges for clients lies in the obscurity, difficulty in locating, lack of guarantees, or doubts associated with these talents, leading to missed opportunities and deals.
NAIIVE serves as an intermediary and a guarantor, facilitating collaboration between clients and these talents, ensuring that they can fully leverage their skills, while clients receive assurances regarding the sustainability of their projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>job</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f92_job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f92_job/</guid>
      <description>send a email to naiive@email.com We’re excited to hear from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f93_partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f93_partnership/</guid>
      <description>email : naiive@email.com / still.lkmn@hotmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
