<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NAIIVE</title>
    <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NAIIVE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://naiiveprojects.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>At Glance</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_at_glance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_at_glance/</guid>
      <description>Pages linkexplore a wide range of of content created with ❤️, our goal is to create a clean, readable, &amp;amp; enjoyable page to read without heavy cognitive load.
workspacesService
a service to develop, adapt, and manage technology you envision
deployed_codeProjects
Technical explanation &amp; executable
streamResources
Open resource, for public / general use
Design linkto familiarize our visitors with documents / technical description that often will found when adapting to technology, our website is deliberately designed to look like a docs / admin panel, it is also hoped that this design will make it easier for visitors to navigate this website, where all content can be reached very easily by using menu panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/1_general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/1_general/</guid>
      <description>Overview linkTechnology is no longer something expensive or difficult to reach. but unfortunately this often only applies to individuals or companies that operating in this field.
Problem linkFor the rest of individuals or companies, technology is something foreign or unreachable, even tho it cannot be denied nowadays technology and automation is take very important role to not only speed up, expand, bring efficiency, event to stay afloat for these individuals or companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/2_request/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/2_request/</guid>
      <description>email : naiive@email.com / still.lkmn@hotmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ ID ] Sphere Draft</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/11_software/1_sphere_draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/1_service/11_software/1_sphere_draft/</guid>
      <description>warning this service only available in Indonesia, you can apply / request this service to be available in your country. Aplikasi Virtual Tour identik dengan luxury / membingungkan dimana hanya sebagian perusahaan / individu yang dapat memanfaatkannya, kami menawarkan jasa pengembangan / pembuatan virtual tour baik dalam bentuk jasa maupun pembuatan software untuk berbagai platform, yang dapat bersaing baik dari segi harga, kualitas, support, juga fleksibilitas.
di rekomendasikan untuk melihat layanan-layanan yang telah tersedia, berikut beberapa layanan dengan poin perbedaan dengan jasa yang kami tawarkan tanpa pengulangan poin yang di sampaikan :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AISE</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/1_aise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/1_aise/</guid>
      <description>General linkAISE is an software build in godot engine that provide user with various tools to create / modify images, it designed as mobile application and initially was made for attempt to integrate the latest technology of artificial intelligent.
Resources AI features Online features Offline features url type description Itch.io page, HTML5 executable &amp;amp; more user friendly explanation Android installer as apk target platform IOS N/A target platform Windows portable as exe in zip for testing, main development operating system MacOS unknown as zip for testing, untested / reported Linux portable as x86_64 in zip for testing, untested / reported Use Stable Diffusion Served by AI Horde Models Text to Image Image to Image ControlNet Tiling &amp;amp; More LoRA by Civit AI Style Prompt injection using CheatSheet Discovery (Social) Reporting Tool Version Checking Text Translation Google Translate API Image Optimization Resmush API image editing sketch gallery Motivation linkAISE initially build for only limited amount of time (max 1 day), where the goal is to integrate latest technology of Artificial Intelligent as fast as possible for proof of concept and as a basic design practice for Mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motive</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/2_motive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/2_project/2_motive/</guid>
      <description> warning Caution - This page is in progress. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAIIVE Website</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/1_naiive_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/1_naiive_website/</guid>
      <description>Thread link weight : int # thread weight for indexing title : string icon : string icon path. ref https://fonts.google.com/icons description : string lead : string date : date lastmod : date draft : bool images : array toc : bool Add Alerts linkPage alerts can be added to your markdown using the following shortcode:
{{&amp;lt; alert text=&amp;#34;This is the default alert. It consists of a default theme colour and icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nv.gd.core</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/2_nv.gd.core/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/6_document/61_documentation/2_nv.gd.core/</guid>
      <description>Brief linkNAIIVE.GODOT.Core is set of class, modules, &amp;amp; reusable objects we often use as starting point or to speed up development process
warning Caution - This page is in progress. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f90_about_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f90_about_us/</guid>
      <description>NAIIVE is a decentralized Organization / Company operating in various fields.
initialy NAIIVE was formed by opportunities where many talents were underappreciated / had no connections / had no choice which ultimately hampered or stopped these talents from improving or living with their talents.
one of the problems for clients are that these talents don&amp;rsquo;t have a name yet / difficult to find / don&amp;rsquo;t have guarantees / or doubtful, which ultimately results in lost opportunities / deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>job</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f92_job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f92_job/</guid>
      <description>send a email to naiive@email.com We’re excited to hear from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership</title>
      <link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f93_partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/docs/f93_partnership/</guid>
      <description>email : naiive@email.com / still.lkmn@hotmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
