<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NAIIVE – Blog</title><link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on NAIIVE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 20:54:44 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/glossary/</guid><description>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;code>Decentralize&lt;/code>&lt;/strong> means &lt;strong>distributing control&lt;/strong> or decision-making authority away from a central entity, promoting transparency, and reducing single points of failure.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;code>streamline&lt;/code>&lt;/strong> refers to the act of &lt;strong>simplifying and improving a process&lt;/strong> or system by eliminating unnecessary steps.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;code>executable&lt;/code>&lt;/strong> is a file or &lt;strong>program that can be run or executed&lt;/strong> on a computer or electronic device.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;code>Git&lt;/code>&lt;/strong> is a &lt;strong>system that allows its user to track changes&lt;/strong>, collaborate with others, and manage software development projects efficiently. Most Known Service: &lt;em>&lt;strong>GitHub&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;code>Source code&lt;/code>&lt;/strong> is a &lt;strong>Assets, resource, and human-readable text-based document&lt;/strong> written in specific programming language that serves as blueprint for how a computer program should function.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;code>Open-source&lt;/code>&lt;/strong> refers to software or projects where the &lt;code>source code&lt;/code> is made available to the public. This means that &lt;strong>anyone can view, modify, and distribute it.&lt;/strong> It&amp;rsquo;s like having access to the recipe for a dish, you can not only cook it but also add your own ingredients.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>&lt;code>IoT&lt;/code>&lt;/strong> (Internet of Things) is a network of physical objects that can &lt;strong>collect and exchange data over the internet.&lt;/strong> It enables everyday items to communicate, share data, and make autonomous decisions.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Project status</title><link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/project_status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 20:54:44 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/project_status/</guid><description>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Not Started&lt;/strong>: initial status when a project has been defined but work hasn&amp;rsquo;t begun yet.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Planning&lt;/strong>: This stage involves creating a project plan, defining requirements, and preparing for development.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Needs Feedback&lt;/strong>: The project is waiting for feedback or approval from stakeholders.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Documentation&lt;/strong>: Focusing on creating or updating project documentation.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Testing&lt;/strong>: The project is in the testing phase, which can include unit testing, integration testing, and user acceptance testing.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Refactoring&lt;/strong>: The project is being refactored to improve maintainability or performance.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Alpha/Beta Testing&lt;/strong>: The software is being tested by a select group of users before general release.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Release Candidate&lt;/strong>: The software is in its final stage of testing before being released to the public.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>In Progress&lt;/strong>: The development work is actively underway.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>On Hold&lt;/strong>: The project has been temporarily suspended but may resume in the future.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Canceled&lt;/strong>: The project has been officially canceled, and no further work will be done on it.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Completed&lt;/strong>: The project has been finished successfully and meets all the requirements.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Delayed&lt;/strong>: The project is behind schedule, and the team is working on catching up.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Blocked&lt;/strong>: Work on the project is blocked by an issue or dependency.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Reopened&lt;/strong>: The project was considered completed but has been reopened due to issues or new requirements.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Monitoring&lt;/strong>: The project is live, and monitoring and maintenance activities are ongoing.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Automation and application</title><link>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/automation_and_application/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:09:42 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://naiiveprojects.github.io/blog/automation_and_application/</guid><description>
&lt;p>Automation and application are related and it can be quite challenging to determine whether a project is automation or application.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>due to our commitment it is most likely that we are building interface on top of the automation service, therefore we created a small standard that can be one of the considerations in determining whether a project is included in the automation or application category.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Automation&lt;/strong>: Automation involves the use of technology, software, or machinery to perform tasks or processes with &lt;code>minimal human intervention&lt;/code>. It aims to streamline and optimize repetitive or complex tasks by using predefined rules or algorithms.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Application&lt;/strong>: An application, is a software program or computer program designed to perform specific tasks or functions. its a &lt;code>user-facing programs&lt;/code>.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>automation is a broader concept that encompasses the use of technology to automate tasks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>application is a specific type of software program designed for a particular purpose and often used by end-users. however, Some applications incorporate automation features to enhance functionality and efficiency.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>